{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622694","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622694","name":"Annex","address":"24 Adams W.","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Andrus McDonald","licenseNumber":"262321","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"","geojson":{"id":"51622694","type":"Feature","geometry":null,"properties":{"name":"Annex","owner":"Andrus McDonald","address":"24 Adams W.","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"262321","establishmentid":"51622694","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"4/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"57398","inspectionDate":"2022-02-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."}]},{"inspectionid":"53311","inspectionDate":"2020-10-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45619","inspectionDate":"2019-03-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2018-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BAR (MAIN)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622694"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}